tgv.com.my 2013-11-04

# TGV Cinemas - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy has been incorporated within the TGV Cinemas Sdn Bhd("TGV") Terms and Conditions and terms and expressions used in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning as they have been given in the Terms and Conditions.

TGV recognises the importance of your privacy and will not disclose personally identifiable information to any third party. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy TGV reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If you do not agree please do not use TGV Services.

Our primary purpose in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with safe, smooth and efficient services. This allows us to provide TGV services safer and easier. We only collect Personal Information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. At times, we may examine, compare and review your Personal Information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

TGV checks and processes credit card transactions with its bankers and carries out this online verification with the bank over a secure line.

In making any payment by credit card you must input the cardholder's name, your credit card number, card expiry date, CVC code(ie. 3-digit number shown at the reverse side of your credit card), contact telephone number and email address if applicable. The card details are encrypted before being transferred over the internet and all incoming credit card payments are processed by TGV on your behalf using the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) protocol.

In addition to the details you supply when purchasing and using the website, TGV may collect information about your tastes and preferences based on your use of the website. The collection of information may include the analysis of website traffic and purchasing behaviour, including the use of cookies. TGV may use this information and the information supplied by you when registering to inform you about changes to the website and other remote sales channels, new services, film and cinema news, film performance times and competitions or offers that you might find interesting via e-newsletters.

TGV will not pass your details to any third party or company except those that we use to perform statistical analysis or manage communications on our behalf. All communications will come from TGV but we may choose to involve carefully selected third parties or companies from time to time in our communications. You can un-register at anytime via the link provided in the e-newsletter.

From time to time, TGV will compile aggregate statistics about the services and may share them with reputable third parties. These statistics will not contain information that would enable any third party to identify you personally.

TGV reserves the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with all applicable laws and lawful requests by the appropriate authorities, to operate its systems or for its own protection or that of its other users. TGV also reserves the right to disclose individually identifiable information to third parties where a complaint arises concerning your use of the TGV Website or other remote sales channels, and we consider that use to be inconsistent with our Terms and Conditions.

TGV will not store any financial details other than your 16-digit credit card number to which is linked to your ticket booking. Access to our secure web server is strictly controlled.

When you use a link from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other websites is subject to that websites own rules and policies.
